https://corporate.univision.com/privacy-policy/

Effective August 7, 2012
Univision.net (the “Site”), which is owned and operated by Univision Communications Inc. along with its network affiliates (whether existing now or in the future) including Univision Network, UniMas Network, UniMas Television Group, Inc. and Galavision (collectively “Univision” or “we”), provides general information about Univision products and services.
By submitting information on this Site, you expressly give us permission to receive, store, process and use such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy also constitutes part of the Terms of Use that govern your use of the Site.  BY USING THE SITE, YOU ACCEPT AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY OUR TERMS OF USE AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
In this Privacy Policy, we inform you as to which information we may collect from or about you on the Site, how we may use such information, the choices you have regarding our use of such information, and your ability to review, update and correct such information.
1. Types of Information We Collect
1.1 Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”):  When you join our emailing list to receive our newsletters and other communications via email we collect your email address.  We also collect PII that you choose to give us in your communications with us, including, for example, surveys and feedback forms you may complete on the Site.
1.2 Aggregate and Anonymous Information (“AAI”):  We also collect aggregate and anonymous information (“AAI”) on the Site.  AAI cannot identify or be linked to a specific individual.  For example, we collect user traffic data and total page views in a given time period, average amount of time users spend on the Site, how many times a particular piece of content on the Site was viewed or downloaded by our users, etc.  We may also combine information about individual users to generate aggregate data that reflects activities, habits, preferences, interests, etc. about our users as a group.
1.3 User Activity Information (“UAI”):  In addition, we collect certain user activity information (“UAI”) on the Site.  For example, our Site servers automatically collect and log “clickstream data” for all visitors to the Site, such as IP addresses (which are numerical numbers that are automatically assigned to users’ computers and mobile devices when they are surfing the Internet), page requests, pages visited, content viewed, clicks and search queries made, etc.  If and to the extent we use any UAI in a manner that identifies a specific user individually (e.g., if we link or associate such information with a specific user), it will be treated as PII.  Otherwise, all UAI will be treated as AAI.
2. What We May Do With Your Information
2.1 We use your PII to communicate with you and provide information requested by you or information that may interest you (e.g., information about our network programming line-ups, programming offers, network launch, etc.).  The collection of PII also enables us to know and understand our users so that we can improve the Site and make it as appealing and useful as possible for our users.  We may also use your email address (if you have subscribed to our emailing list) to send you notices of a transactional, administrative or relationship nature or as required by law, such as notification of a material change in this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms of Use for the Site, notification of an actual or suspected security breach that affects your information stored by or for us, public relations announcements, etc.
2.2 From time to time, we may share your PII for internal purposes (e.g., internal evaluation and research, internal marketing and operational uses, etc.) with our affiliated companies (e.g., The Univision Network Limited Partnership, Univision Television Group, Inc., Univision Radio, Inc., Univision Interactive Media Inc., UniMas Television Group, Inc., UniMas Network, Inc., Univision Management Co., Galavision, Inc., etc.).  We do not, however, share PII with third parties that are not affiliated with us, except in the following circumstances:
We may disclose PII to third-party service providers (e.g., providers of hosting, maintenance, and/or data processing services for the Site, market research and consulting firms engaged by us, etc.) who need to access such information in order to perform services to us.  Generally, we require that our service providers use information shared by us solely for the purposes of performing services to us and that they maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of such information and not further disclose the information to others.
We may disclose PII to others if doing so is required by law or, in our good faith belief, is reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with legal process (including a court order or subpoena); (2) cooperate with law enforcement; (3) enforce this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms of Use for the Site; (4) respond to an emergency; or (5) protect the rights, property or safety of Univision, members of our users, and/or the public.
We may transfer PII as part of our assets if we (or parts of our businesses) are, sold or transferred to, merged with, or acquired by, a third party.  Upon such transfer, the privacy policy of the acquiring entity may govern the further use of your information.
2.3 Given the anonymous, non-personally identifiable nature of AAI, there are no restrictions under this Privacy Policy on how we may use, disclose, sell, or otherwise share such information.  For example, we may freely share AAI with third parties for marketing, advertising, research, and/or other business purposes.  We may also freely share AAI with our service providers in order for them to perform services to us.
3. Information Access & Opt –Out
3.1 If you have provided PII to us, you can request to access and update your information by fax at (646) 478-9627 or via email at privacy@univision.net and make your request and provide any necessary information.
3.2 To opt out of receiving programming and other marketing information from the Site, please contact us by fax at (646) 478-9627 or via email at privacy@univision.net and make your request and provide any necessary information.  For electronic mailings, you can also make your opt-out request by changing your preferences with respect to emails and electronic newsletters in your user profile on the Site, or by using the opt-out means (e.g., an “unsubscribe” link) provided in an applicable email that you have previously received from the Site.
3.4 We will endeavor to honor your opt-out request as soon as practicable (or within such applicable time period as required by law).  Your opt out election, once processed by us, will stop, on a going-forward basis, all further electronic mailings from the Site; EXCEPT, however, that your opt-out will NOT apply to email communications from us of a transactional, administrative or relationship nature, or as required by law, such as notification of a material change in this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms of Use for the Site, notification of an actual or suspected security breach that affects your information stored by or for us, public relations announcements, etc.
4. Data Retention
We will retain your PII for as long as your account on the Site is active or as needed to provide you products or services, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and/or enforce our agreements.  AAI and UAI (if not personally identifiable) may be retained indefinitely.
5. Protecting Children
We take special care to protect the safety and privacy of children.  The Site and its products and services are NOT intended for or directed to children.  We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from or about users under age 13.
Children under age 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online or through mobile devices.  If you are a parent or legal guardian, we urge you to participate in your child’s online and mobile activities and to use parental control or other Internet and/or mobile filtering technology to supervise your child’s access to the Internet.
6. Cookies and Similar Technologies
The Site uses “cookies.”  A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from an internet server and stored in your computer.  Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our content, products and services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size, process your requests and comments, and/or to analyze your visiting patterns.  You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it, or you can choose to routinely and manually delete the cookies stored in your computer.  If you choose to disable or reject cookies, you may still be able to access some parts of the Site, but you may not have full access to all products and services of the Site.  For more information on how to manage cookies in your web browser, seehttp://www.aboutcookies.org.
7. Security
Protecting the security of PII that you share with us is important to us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet or any mobile or wireless network and no data storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, while we strive to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from or on the Site, and you do so at your own risk.  By providing your email address to us, you acknowledge and agree that we may notify you by email in the event of a breach of security involving your PII.
8. Links to Other Sites
8.1 The Site contains links to websites operated and maintained by our affiliates, such as Univision.com, a consumer-facing site operated and maintained by Univision Interactive Media, Inc. (each, a “Linked Affiliate Site”).  Such Linked Affiliate Sites have their own privacy policies which have terms and conditions that differ from those in this Privacy Policy.  When you visit a Linked Affiliate Site (e.g., Univision.com), this Privacy Policy no longer applies, and any information collected from or about you on such Linked Affiliate Site will be governed by and subject to that site’s privacy policy.
8.2 From time to time, the Site may also provide links to websites operated and maintained by third parties that are not affiliated with us (each, a “Linked Unaffiliated Site”).  We have no control over such third parties, their sites, or their products or services.  Once you enter a Linked Unaffiliated Site, this Privacy Policy will no longer apply, and any information collected from or about you on that site will be governed by and subject to the privacy policies and practices of that third party.
9. Policy Changes
From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy in whole or in part, to accommodate new technology, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes.  We will provide notice to you if these changes are material and, where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent.  If you are a registered user of the Site, we may notify you of material changes to this Privacy Policy via email and/or may ask you to affirmatively acknowledge and consent to such changes (e.g., by checking a box or clicking a button) at the time of your next account login on the Site.
10. Additional Information
We shall not be liable under any circumstances for any special, incidental or consequential damages that result from the use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy or that result from any content, material, product or service made available on the Site, even if we have been advised of the possibility of such damages.  This section should be read together with our Terms of Use.
Please enter a valid e-mail address.
By clicking submit you agree to our Privacy Policy and Terms of service.
Thank you, you'll be receiving newsletter updates from us in your email inbox.
Okay
Loading
